[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "title": "Toplama",
    "subtitle": "Temel Toplama",
    "time": "0.5",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "question": "3+2 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["4", "5", "6", "7"],
        "correctAnswer": "5"
      },
      {
        "question": "4+3 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["6", "7", "5", "8"],
        "correctAnswer": "7"
      },
      {
        "question": "5+8 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["12", "13", "14", "11"],
        "correctAnswer": "13"
      },
      {
        "question": "6+6 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["11", "12", "13", "14"],
        "correctAnswer": "12"
      },
      {
        "question": "2+7 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["8", "9", "6", "10"],
        "correctAnswer": "9"
      },
      {
        "question": "4+9 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["14", "15", "16", "13"],
        "correctAnswer": "13"
      },
      {
        "question": "7+8 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["14", "15", "16", "13"],
        "correctAnswer": "15"
      },
      {
        "question": "3+4 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["5", "7", "8", "6"],
        "correctAnswer": "7"
      }
    ]
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "title": "Çıkarma",
    "subtitle": "Temel Çıkarma",
    "time": "5",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "question": "8-3 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["5", "6", "4", "3"],
        "correctAnswer": "5"
      },
      {
        "question": "7-4 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
        "correctAnswer": "3"
      },
      {
        "question": "9-2 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["6", "7", "5", "8"],
        "correctAnswer": "7"
      },
      {
        "question": "12-5 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["7", "8", "9", "6"],
        "correctAnswer": "7"
      },
      {
        "question": "15-8 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["7", "6", "8", "9"],
        "correctAnswer": "7"
      },
      {
        "question": "10-3 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["7", "6", "8", "5"],
        "correctAnswer": "7"
      }
    ]
  },
 {
  "id": 1,
  "title": "Çarpma",
  "subtitle": "3'ler, 4'ler, 5'ler, 6'lar, 7'ler, 8'ler, 9'lar, 10'lar",
  "time": "2",
  "questionList": [
    {
      "question": "7x5=?",
      "options": [
        "25",
        "40",
        "35",
        "30"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "35"
    },
    {
      "question": "5x9=?",
      "options": [
        "55",
        "45",
        "50",
        "60"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "45"
    },
    {
      "question": "3x4=?",
      "options": [
        "14",
        "12",
        "10",
        "11"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "8x6=?",
      "options": [
        "52",
        "48",
        "50",
        "55"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "48"
    },
    {
      "question": "4x9=?",
      "options": [
        "40",
        "35",
        "38",
        "36"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "36"
    },
    {
      "question": "10x7=?",
      "options": [
        "75",
        "80",
        "70",
        "85"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "70"
    },
    {
      "question": "9x3=?",
      "options": [
        "33",
        "24",
        "30",
        "27"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "27"
    },
    {
      "question": "6x8=?",
      "options": [
        "56",
        "48",
        "55",
        "52"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "48"
    },
    {
      "question": "7x9=?",
      "options": [
        "72",
        "66",
        "63",
        "65"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "63"
    },
    {
      "question": "5x7=?",
      "options": [
        "50",
        "40",
        "45",
        "35"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "35"
    },
    {
      "question": "9x5=?",
      "options": [
        "55",
        "50",
        "45",
        "60"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "45"
    },
    {
      "question": "6x4=?",
      "options": [
        "26",
        "20",
        "22",
        "24"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "24"
    },
    {
      "question": "3x8=?",
      "options": [
        "24",
        "28",
        "22",
        "26"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "24"
    },
    {
      "question": "4x6=?",
      "options": [
        "24",
        "28",
        "22",
        "20"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "24"
    },
    {
      "question": "10x3=?",
      "options": [
        "33",
        "28",
        "32",
        "30"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "30"
    },
    {
      "question": "8x9=?",
      "options": [
        "72",
        "70",
        "74",
        "75"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "72"
    },
    {
      "question": "5x3=?",
      "options": [
        "18",
        "16",
        "15",
        "14"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "15"
    },
    {
      "question": "6x9=?",
      "options": [
        "54",
        "60",
        "56",
        "55"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "54"
    },
    {
      "question": "9x8=?",
      "options": [
        "72",
        "70",
        "74",
        "78"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "72"
    },
    {
      "question": "3x6=?",
      "options": [
        "22",
        "20",
        "17",
        "18"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "7x10=?",
      "options": [
        "80",
        "75",
        "70",
        "60"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "70"
    },
    {
      "question": "4x3=?",
      "options": [
        "11",
        "12",
        "14",
        "15"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "12"
    },
    {
      "question": "5x8=?",
      "options": [
        "42",
        "38",
        "45",
        "40"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "40"
    },
    {
      "question": "6x5=?",
      "options": [
        "32",
        "35",
        "28",
        "30"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "30"
    },
    {
      "question": "8x4=?",
      "options": [
        "34",
        "32",
        "36",
        "30"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "32"
    },
    {
      "question": "10x5=?",
      "options": [
        "45",
        "60",
        "50",
        "55"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "50"
    },
    {
      "question": "9x4=?",
      "options": [
        "36",
        "38",
        "40",
        "37"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "36"
    },
    {
      "question": "6x7=?",
      "options": [
        "45",
        "42",
        "40",
        "48"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "42"
    },
    {
      "question": "7x8=?",
      "options": [
        "58",
        "60",
        "55",
        "56"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "56"
    },
    {
      "question": "8x7=?",
      "options": [
        "55",
        "56",
        "58",
        "60"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "56"
    },
    {
      "question": "4x5=?",
      "options": [
        "23",
        "25",
        "20",
        "22"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "20"
    },
    {
      "question": "10x8=?",
      "options": [
        "90",
        "80",
        "85",
        "100"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "80"
    },
    {
      "question": "7x6=?",
      "options": [
        "45",
        "40",
        "42",
        "44"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "42"
    },
    {
      "question": "6x3=?",
      "options": [
        "17",
        "18",
        "20",
        "16"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "18"
    },
    {
      "question": "9x6=?",
      "options": [
        "50",
        "52",
        "54",
        "56"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "54"
    },
    {
      "question": "10x4=?",
      "options": [
        "45",
        "35",
        "40",
        "50"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "40"
    }
  ]
},

  {
    "id": 4,
    "title": "Karışık",
    "subtitle": "Toplama, Çıkarma, Çarpma",
    "time": "6",
    "questionList": [
      {
        "question": "4+5 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["10", "9", "11", "12"],
        "correctAnswer": "9"
      },
      {
        "question": "7-2 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["5", "6", "4", "3"],
        "correctAnswer": "5"
      },
      {
        "question": "3x3 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["9", "8", "7", "10"],
        "correctAnswer": "9"
      },
      {
        "question": "6x4 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["24", "25", "22", "23"],
        "correctAnswer": "24"
      },
      {
        "question": "8-4 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["5", "4", "3", "6"],
        "correctAnswer": "4"
      },
      {
        "question": "5+7 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["13", "14", "15", "12"],
        "correctAnswer": "12"
      },
      {
        "question": "9x2 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["19", "18", "17", "16"],
        "correctAnswer": "18"
      },
      {
        "question": "10-6 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["4", "5", "6", "3"],
        "correctAnswer": "4"
      },
      {
        "question": "3+6 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["9", "10", "8", "7"],
        "correctAnswer": "9"
      },
      {
        "question": "12-7 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["5", "6", "4", "3"],
        "correctAnswer": "5"
      },
      {
        "question": "4x5 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["20", "21", "19", "22"],
        "correctAnswer": "20"
      },
      {
        "question": "6x8 kaçtır?",
        "options": ["48", "46", "47", "45"],
        "correctAnswer": "48"
      }
    ]
  }
]
